Finding Aid for the William and Lee Bell Scripts for Television Soap Operas PASC.0096
UCLA Library Special Collections
- DAYS OF OUR LIVES
  - Prod. #2790-2801. Aired: 12/13/76-12/28/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 61)
  - Prod. #1512-1541. Aired: 10/20/71-12/17/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 62)
  - Prod. #1542-1574. Aired: 12/20/71-02/03/72. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 63)
  - Prod. #1575-1604. Aired: 02/04/72-03/16/72. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 64)
  - Prod. #1605-1636. Aired: 03/17/72-05/01/72. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 65)
  - Prod. #1637-1660. Aired: 05/02/72-06/06/72. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 66)
  - Prod. #937-966. Aired: 07/23/69-09/05/69. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 67)
  - Prod. #967-996. Aired: 09/08/69-10/17/69. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 68)
  - Prod. #997-1031. Aired: 10/20/69-12/12/69. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 69)
  - Prod. #1032-1061. Aired: 12/15/69-01/19/70. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 70)
  - Prod. #1062-1076. Aired: 01/26/70-02/13/70. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 71)
  - Prod. #2456-2469. Aired: 08/22/75-09/10/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 72)
  - Prod. #2470-2481. Aired: 09/12/75-09/29/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 73)
  - Prod. #2482-2493. Aired: 09/30/75-10/15/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 74)
  - Prod. #2494-2508. Aired: 10/16/75-11/06/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 75)
  - Prod. #2509-2520. Aired: 11/07/75-11/24/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 76)
  - Prod. #1960-1989. Aired: (TAPE)08/20/73-10/08/73. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 77)
  - Prod. #1990-2019. Aired: (TAPE)10/09/73-12/06/73. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 78)
  - Prod. #2020-2049. Aired: 12/07/73-01/16/74. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 79)
  - Prod. #2050-2079. Aired: 01/18/74-02/28/74. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 80)
  - Prod. #2080-2099. Aired: 03/01/74-03/28/74. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 81)
  - Prod. #2100-2114. Aired: 03/29/74-04/19/74. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 82)
  - Prod. #2934-2948. Aired: 07/04/77-07/22/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 83)
  - Prod. #2949-2963. Aired: 07/25/77-08/12/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 84)
  - Prod. #2964-2978. Aired: 08/15/77-09/02/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 85)
  - Prod. #2979-2993. Aired: 09/05/77-09/23/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 86)
  - Prod. #2386-2440. Aired: 05/16/75-06/05/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 87)
  - Prod. #2401-2412. Aired: 06/06/75-06/23/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 88)
  - Prod. #2413-2428. Aired: 06/24/75-07/15/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 89)
  - Prod. #2429-2431. Aired: 07/26/75-07/31/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 90)
  - Prod. #2432-2455. Aired: 08/01/75-08/21/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 91)
  - Prod. #667-696. Aired: 06/25/68-08/06/68. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 92)
  - Prod. #697-726. Aired: 08/07/68-09/18/68. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 93)
  - Prod. #727-756. Aired: 09/19/68-11/06/68. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 94)
  - Prod. #757-781. Aired: 11/07/68-12/12/68. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 95)
  - Prod. #782-801. Aired: 12/13/68-12/31/68. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 96)
  - Prod. #802-826. Aired: 01/13/69-02/17/69. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 97)
  - Prod. #827-856. Aired: 02/18/69-04/01/69. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 98)
  - Prod. #857-886. Aired: 04/02/69-05/13/69. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 99)
  - Prod. #887-906. Aired: 05/14/69-06/17/69. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 100)
  - Prod. #912-936. Aired: 06/18/69-07/22/69. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 101)
  - Prod. #1077-1106. Aired: 02/16/70-03/27/70. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 102)
  - Prod. #1107-1136. Aired: 03/30/70-05/08/70. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 103)
  - Prod. #1137-1166. Aired: 05/12/70-06/22/70. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 104)
  - Prod. #1167-1191. Aired: 06/23/70-07/27/70. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 105)
  - Prod. #1192-1221. Aired: 07/28/70-09/07/70. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 106)
  - Prod. #2588-2602. Aired: 03/02/76-03/23/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 107)
  - Prod. #2603-2617. Aired: 03/22/76-04/12/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 108)
  - Prod. #2618-2632. Aired: 04/13/76-05/03/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 109)
  - Prod. #2633-2644. Aired: 05/04/76-05/19/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 110)
  - Prod. #2645-2659. Aired: 05/20/76-06/09/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 111)
  - Prod. #2866-2880. Aired: 03/30/77-04/19/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 112)
  - Prod. #2881-2882. Aired: 04/20/77-04/21/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 113)
  - Prod. #2884-2896. Aired: 04/25/77-05/01/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 113)
  - Prod. #2897-2911. Aired: 05/12/77-06/01/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 114)
  - Prod. #2912-2926. Aired: 06/02/77-06/22/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 115)
  - Prod. #2927-2933. Aired: 06/23/77-06/30/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 116)
  - Prod. #2994-2997. Aired: 09/26/77-09/28/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 116)
  - Prod. #2660-2672. Aired: 06/10/76-06/28/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 117)
  - Prod. #2673-2687. Aired: 06/29/76-07/19/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 118)
  - Prod. #2688-2702. Aired: 07/21/76-08/10/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 119)
  - Prod. #2703-2717. Aired: 08/11/76-08/30/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 120)
  - Prod. #2718-2732. Aired: 09/01/76-09/21/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 121)
  - Prod. #1951-2050. Aired: (TAPE)08/01/73-02/01/74. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 122)
  - Prod. #2061-2160. Aired: 02/04/74-(TAPE)06/10/74. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 123)
  - Prod. #2161-2260. Aired: (TAPE)06/11/74-NOT DATED. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 124)
  - Prod. #2261-2370. Aired: (TAPE)10/30/74-NOT DATED. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 125)
  - Aired:. Notes: DRAFTS AND PROJECTIONS 1966-74. (Box 126)
  - Aired:. Notes: DRAFTS, PROJECTIONS, OUTLINES 1974-77. (Box 127)
  - Aired:. Notes: CORRESPONDENCE Feb. 1977. (Box 128)
  - Aired:. Notes: CORRESPONDENCE 1969-74. (Box 129)
  - Prod. #206----. Aired: 08/29/66. Notes: SCRIPT. (Box 130)
  - Prod. #662-666. Aired: 06/18/68-06/24/68. Notes: SCRIPTS; "CONTACT PERFORMANCE STATUS". (Box 130)
  - Prod. #3641-----. Aired: 03/26/80. Notes: SCRIPT. (Box 130)
  - Prod. #123-124. Aired: 05/02/66-05/03/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 160)
  - Prod. #137-164. Aired: 05/20/66-06/24/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 160)
  - Prod. #168-172. Aired: 07/05/66-07/11/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 160)
  - Prod. #173-202. Aired: 07/12/66-08/23/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 161)
  - Prod. #203-228. Aired: 08/24/66-09/23/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 162)
  - Prod. #229-259. Aired: 09/29/66-11/10/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 163)
  - Prod. #260-290. Aired: 11/11/66-12/27/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 164)
  - Prod. #291-319. Aired: 12/28/66-02/07/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 165)
  - Prod. #320-350. Aired: 02/08/67-03/22/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 166)
  - Prod. #351-386. Aired: 03/23/67-05/12/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 167)
  - Prod. #387-421. Aired: 05/16/67-07/04/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 168)
  - Prod. #422-456. Aired: 07/04/67-08/22/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 169)
  - Prod. #457-491. Aired: 08/23/67-10/10/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 170)
  - Prod. #492-521. Aired: 10/11/67-11/29/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 171)
  - Prod. #522-546, 567-571. Aired: 11/30/67-02/08/68. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 172)
  - Prod. #572-601. Aired: 02/09/68-03/21/68. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 173)
  - Prod. #602-631. Aired: 03/22/68-05/06/68. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 174)
  - Prod. #632-656. Aired: 05/07/68-06/10/68. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 175)
  - Prod. #169-183. Aired: 12/07/64-07/19/66. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 176)
  - Prod. #206-260. Aired: 08/28/66-11/11/66. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 176)
  - Prod. #261-340. Aired: 11/14/66-03/08/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 177)
  - Prod. #341-447. Aired: 03/09/67-08/09/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 178)
  - Prod. #448-535. Aired: 08/10/67-12/19/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 179)
  - Prod. #536-640. Aired: 12/20/67-05/16/68. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 180)
  - Prod. #641-699. Aired: 05/20/68-08/09/68. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 181)
  - Prod. #700-755. Aired: 08/12/68-10/28/68. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 182)
  - Prod. #756-835. Aired: 10/29/68-02/28/69. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 183)
  - Prod. #836-909. Aired: 03/03/69-06/13/69. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 184)
  - Prod. #910-969. Aired: 06/16/69-09/10/69. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 185)
  - Prod. #970-1039. Aired: 09/10/69-12/24/69. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 186)
  - Prod. #1040-1108. Aired: 12/25/69-04/01/70. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 187)
  - Prod. #1110-1179. Aired: 04/02/70-07/09/70. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 188)
  - Prod. #1180-1249. Aired: 07/10/70-10/15/70. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 189)
  - Prod. #1250-1319. Aired: 10/16/70-01/28/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 190)
  - Prod. #1320-1389. Aired: 05/10/71-08/06/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 191)
  - Prod. #1390-1454. Aired: 01/29/71-05/07/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 192)
  - Prod. #1455-1505. Aired: 08/09/71-(TAPE)10/11/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 193)
  - Prod. #1506-1534. Aired: (TAPE)10/12/71-12/08/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 194)
- GUIDING LIGHT, THE
  - Prod. 6/57-1/58. Aired: 06/26/57-01/31/58. Notes: SCRIPTS, NOTES, AND CORRESPONDENCE. (Box 144)
- LAURA
  - Aired: NOT DATED. Notes: SERIES IDEA. (Box 130)
- LOVE IS A MANY SPLENDORED THING
  - Aired: NOT DATED. Notes: SERIES IDEA. (Box 130)
- MANY WAYS OF LOVE, THE
  - Aired: NOT DATED. Notes: SERIES IDEA. (Box 130)
- OUR PRIVATE WORLD
  - Prod. #1-21. Aired: 05/05/65-07/14/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 142)
  - Prod. #22-38. Aired: 07/16/65-09/10/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 143)
- YOUNG AND THE RESTLESS, THE
  - Prod. #1-109. Aired: (UNDATED)-(TAPE)08/25/73. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 211)
  - Prod. #110-169. Aired: (TAPE)08/24/73-11/16/73. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 212)
  - Prod. #170-229. Aired: 12/07/73-03/01/74. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 213)
  - Prod. #230-289. Aired: 03/04/74-05/24/74. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 214)
  - Prod. #290-349. Aired: 05/27/74-08/24/74. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 215)
  - Prod. #350-399. Aired: 08/20/74-11/02/74. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 216)
  - Prod. #400-459. Aired: 11/05/74-01/29/75. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 217)
  - Prod. #460-529. Aired: 01/31/75-05/07/75. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 218)
  - Prod. #530-609. Aired: 05/08/75-08/28/75. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 219)
  - Prod. #610-689. Aired: 08/29/75-12/19/75. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 220)
  - Prod. #690-769. Aired: 12/22/75-04/13/76. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 221)
  - Prod. #770-839. Aired: 04/14/76-07/20/76. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 222)
  - Prod. #840-899. Aired: 07/02/76-10/13/76. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 223)
  - Prod. #900-969. Aired: 10/14/76-01/24/77. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 224)
  - Prod. #970-1027. Aired: 02/07/77-04/05/77. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 225)
  - Prod. #1028-1084. Aired: 04/26/77-06/24/77. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 226)
  - Prod. #1085-1151. Aired: 07/21/77-09/21/77. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 227)
  - Prod. #1152-1240. Aired: 10/26/77-02/10/78. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 228)
  - Prod. #1211-1280. Aired: 12/30/77-04/10/78. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 229)
  - Prod. #1281-1330. Aired: 04/11/78-06/19/78. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 230)
  - Prod. #1331-1379. Aired: 06/20/78-08/25/78. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 231)
  - Prod. #1380-1429. Aired: 08/28/78-11/06/78. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 232)
  - Prod. #1430-1489. Aired: 11/07/78-01/31/79. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 233)
  - Prod. #1490-1539. Aired: 02/01/79-04/11/79. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 234)
  - Prod. #1540-1589. Aired: 04/12/79-06/20/79. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 235)
  - Prod. #1590-1639. Aired: 06/21/79-08/29/79. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 236)
  - Prod. #1640-1689. Aired: 08/30/79-11/08/79. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 237)
  - Prod. #1690-1729. Aired: 01/09/79-01/08/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 238)
  - Prod. #1730-1754. Aired: 01/09/80-02/12/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 239)
  - Prod. #1755-1769. Aired: 02/13/80-03/05/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 240)
  - Prod. #1770-1789. Aired: 03/05/80-03/28/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 241)
  - Prod. #1790-1809. Aired: 04/02/80-04/29/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 242)
  - Prod. #1810-1824. Aired: 04/30/80-05/20/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 243)
  - Prod. #1825-1839. Aired: 05/21/80-06/10/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 244)
  - Prod. #1840-1854. Aired: 06/11/80-07/01/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 245)
  - Prod. #1855-1869. Aired: 07/02/80-07/22/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 246)
  - Prod. #1870-1884. Aired: 07/23/80-08/12/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 247)
  - Prod. #1885-1899. Aired: 08/13/80-09/03/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 248)
  - Prod. #1900-1914. Aired: 09/04/80-09/24/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 249)
  - Prod. #1915-1934. Aired: 09/25/80-10/22/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 250)
  - Prod. #1935-1954. Aired: 10/23/80-11/19/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 251)
  - Prod. #1955-1974. Aired: 11/20/80-12/18/80. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 252)
  - Prod. #1975-1989. Aired: 12/19/80-01/12/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 253)
  - Prod. #1990-2004. Aired: 01/13/81-02/03/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 254)
  - Prod. #2005-2024. Aired: 02/04/81-03/04/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 255)
  - Prod. #2025-2039. Aired: 03/05/81-03/25/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 256)
  - Prod. #2040-2054. Aired: 03/26/81-04/15/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 257)
  - Prod. #2055-2069. Aired: 04/16/81-05/06/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 258)
  - Prod. #2070-2084. Aired: 05/07/81-05/27/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 259)
  - Prod. #2085-2104. Aired: 05/28/81-06/25/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 260)
  - Prod. #2105-2129. Aired: 06/26/81-07/30/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 261)
  - Prod. #2130-2149. Aired: 07/31/81-08/27/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 262)
  - Prod. #2150-2169. Aired: 08/28/81-09/25/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 263)
  - Prod. #2170-2189. Aired: 09/28/81-10/23/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 264)
  - Prod. #2190-2209. Aired: 10/26/81-11/23/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 265)
  - Prod. #2210-2229. Aired: 11/24/81-12/22/81. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 266)
  - Prod. #2230-2249. Aired: 12/23/81-01/21/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 267)
  - Prod. #2250-2269. Aired: 01/22/82-02/18/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 268)
  - Prod. #2270-2289. Aired: 02/19/82-03/18/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 269)
  - Prod. #2290-2309. Aired: 03/19/82-04/15/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 270)
  - Prod. #2310-2329. Aired: 04/16/82-05/13/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 271)
  - Prod. #2330-2349. Aired: 05/14/82-06/10/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 272)
  - Prod. #2350-2364. Aired: 06/11/82-07/11/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 273)
  - Prod. #2365-2384. Aired: 07/02/82-07/29/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 274)
  - Prod. #2385-2399. Aired: 07/30/82-08/19/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 275)
  - Prod. #2400-2414. Aired: 08/20/82-09/13/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 276)
  - Prod. #2415-2429. Aired: 09/14/82-10/04/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 277)
  - Prod. #2430-2449. Aired: 10/05/82-11/01/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 278)
  - Prod. #2450-2469. Aired: 11/02/82-12/01/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 279)
  - Prod. #2470-2484. Aired: 12/02/82-12/22/82. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 280)
  - Prod. #2485-2499. Aired: 12/23/82-01/12/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 281)
  - Prod. #2500-2514. Aired: 01/13/83-02/02/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 282)
  - Prod. #2515-2529. Aired: 02/03/83-02/22/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 283)
  - Prod. #2530-2549. Aired: 02/24/83-03/23/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 284)
  - Prod. #2550-2564. Aired: 03/24/83-04/13/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 285)
  - Prod. #2565-2584. Aired: 04/14/83-05/11/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 286)
  - Prod. #2585-2604. Aired: 05/12/83-06/08/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 287)
  - Prod. #2605-2624. Aired: 06/09/83-07/06/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 288)
  - Prod. #2625-2639. Aired: 07/07/83-07/25/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 289)
  - Prod. #2640-2659. Aired: 07/28/83-08/24/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 290)
  - Prod. #2660-2679. Aired: 08/25/83-09/23/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 291)
  - Prod. #2680-2699. Aired: 09/26/83-10/21/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 292)
  - Prod. #2700-2719. Aired: 10/24/83-11/18/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 293)
  - Prod. #2720-2739. Aired: 11/21/83-12/20/83. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 294)
  - Prod. #2740-2759. Aired: 12/21/83-01/18/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 295)
  - Prod. #2760-2779. Aired: 01/19/84-02/15/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 296)
  - Prod. #2785-2799. Aired: 02/23/84-03/14/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 297)
  - Prod. #2800-2819. Aired: 03/15/84-04/11/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 298)
  - Prod. #2820-2834. Aired: 04/12/84-05/02/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 299)
  - Prod. #2835-2854. Aired: 05/03/84-05/30/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 300)
  - Prod. #2855-2874. Aired: 05/31/84-06/27/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 301)
  - Prod. #2875-2894. Aired: 06/28/84-07/25/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 302)
  - Prod. #2895-2914. Aired: 07/26/84-08/22/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 303)
  - Prod. #2915-2934. Aired: 08/23/84-09/21/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 304)
  - Prod. #2935-2949. Aired: 09/24/84-10/12/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 305)
  - Prod. #2950-2964. Aired: 10/15/84-11/02/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 306)
  - Prod. #2965-2979. Aired: 11/05/84-11/27/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 307)
  - Prod. #2980-2994. Aired: 11/28/84-12/18/84. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 308)
  - Prod. #2995-3014. Aired: 12/19/84-01/17/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 309)
  - Prod. #3015-3029. Aired: 01/18/85-02/07/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 310)
  - Prod. #3030-3049. Aired: 02/08/85-03/08/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 311)
  - Prod. #3050-3069. Aired: 03/11/85-(UNDATED). Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 312)
  - Prod. #3070-3084. Aired: 04/18/85-04/26/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 313)
  - Prod. #3085-3099. Aired: 04/29/85-05/17/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 314)
  - Prod. #3100-3124. Aired: 05/20/85-06/07/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 315)
  - Prod. #3115-3129. Aired: 06/10/85-06/28/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 316)
  - Prod. #3130-3149. Aired: 07/01/85-07/26/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 317)
  - Prod. #3150-3164. Aired: 07/29/85-08/16/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 318)
  - Prod. #3165-3184. Aired: 08/19/85-09/17/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 319)
  - Prod. #3185-3199. Aired: 09/18/85-10/08/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 320)
  - Prod. #3200-3219. Aired: 10/09/85-11/05/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 321)
  - Prod. #3220-3234. Aired: 11/06/85-11/26/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 322)
  - Prod. #3235-3249. Aired: 11/27/85-12/19/85. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 323)
  - Prod. #3250-3269. Aired: 12/20/85-01/20/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 324)
  - Prod. #3270-3284. Aired: 01/21/86-02/10/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 325)
  - Prod. #3285-3299. Aired: 02/11/86-03/03/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 326)
  - Prod. #3300-3319. Aired: 03/06/86-04/02/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 327)
  - Prod. #3320-3334. Aired: 04/03/86-04/23/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 328)
  - Prod. #3335-3349. Aired: 04/24/86-05/14/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 329)
  - Prod. #3350-3369. Aired: 05/15/86-06/11/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 330)
  - Prod. #3370-3384. Aired: 06/12/86-07/02/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 331)
  - Prod. #3385-3404. Aired: 07/03/86-07/30/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 332)
  - Prod. #3405-3419. Aired: 07/31/86-08/20/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 333)
  - Prod. #3420-3434. Aired: 08/21/86-09/12/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 334)
  - Prod. #3435-3454. Aired: 09/15/86-10/10/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 335)
  - Prod. #3455-3474. Aired: 10/13/86-11/07/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 336)
  - Prod. #3475-3489. Aired: 11/10/86-12/02/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 337)
  - Prod. #3490-3504. Aired: 12/03/86-12/23/86. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 338)
  - Prod. #3505-3524. Aired: 12/24/86-01/22/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 339)
  - Prod. #3525-3539. Aired: 01/23/87-02/12/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 340)
  - Prod. #3540-3559. Aired: 02/13/87-03/11/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 341)
  - Prod. #3560-3579. Aired: 03/12/87-05/07/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 342)
  - Prod. #3580-3599. Aired: 04/10/87-05/07/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 343)
  - Prod. #3600-3619. Aired: 05/08/87-06/04/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 344)
  - Prod. #3620-3634. Aired: 06/05/87-06/25/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 345)
  - Prod. #3635-3650. Aired: 06/29/87-07/07/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 346)
  - Prod. #1-35. Aired: 03/26/73-05/11/73. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 347)
  - Prod. #36-40. Aired: 05/14/73-05/18/73. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 348)
  - Prod. #61-85. Aired: (TAPE)06/05/73-07/09/73. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 348)
  - Prod. #86-145. Aired: (TAPE))7/10/73-10/30/73. Notes: SCRIPTS (INCOMPLETE). (Box 349)
  - Prod. #3651-3657. Aired: 07/20/87-07/28/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 407)
  - Prod. #3658-3664. Aired: 07/29/87-08/12/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 408)
  - Prod. #3665-3670. Aired: 08/08/87-TBA. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 409)
  - Prod. #3671-3677. Aired: TBA-TBA. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 410)
  - Prod. #3678-3683. Aired: TBA-09/17/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 411)
  - Prod. #3684-3690. Aired: 09/18/87-09/28/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 412)
  - Prod. #3691-3697. Aired: 09/29/87-10/07/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 413)
  - Prod. #3698-3704. Aired: 10/08/87-10/16/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 414)
  - Prod. #3705-3711. Aired: 10/19/87-10/27/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 415)
  - Prod. #3712-3718. Aired: 10/28/87-11/05/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 416)
  - Prod. #3719-3725. Aired: 11/06/87-11/16/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 417)
  - Prod. #3726-3732. Aired: 11/17/87-11/25/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 418)
  - Prod. #3733-3739. Aired: 11/30/87-12/08/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 419)
  - Prod. #3740-3745. Aired: 12/09/87-12/16/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 3742). (Box 420)
  - Prod. #3746-3752. Aired: 12/17/87-12/28/87. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 421)
  - Prod. #3753-3759. Aired: 12/29/87-01/07/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 422)
  - Prod. #3760-3766. Aired: 01/08/88-01/19/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 423)
  - Prod. #3767-3773. Aired: 01/19/88-01/27/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 424)
  - Prod. #3774-3780. Aired: 01/28/88-02/05/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 425)
  - Prod. #3781-3782. Aired: 02/08/88-02/09/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 426)
  - Prod. #3804-3808. Aired: 03/10/88-03/16/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 426)
  - Prod. #3809-3815. Aired: 03/17/88-03/25/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 427)
  - Prod. #3816-3822. Aired: 03/28/88-04/05/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 428)
  - Prod. #3823-3829. Aired: 04/06/88-04/14/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 429)
  - Prod. #3830-3834. Aired: 04/15/88-04/21/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 430)
  - Prod. #3835-3837. Aired: 04/22/88-04/26/88. Notes: SCRIPTS, OUTLINES, AND TIMING SCRIPTS. (Box 431)
  - Prod. #3838-3839. Aired: 04/27/88-04/28/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 431)
  - Prod. #3840-3846. Aired: 04/29/88-05/09/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 432)
  - Prod. #3847-3853. Aired: 05/10/88-05/18/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 433)
  - Prod. #3854-3860. Aired: 05/19/88-05/27/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 434)
  - Prod. #3861-3867. Aired: 05/30/88-06/07/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 435)
  - Prod. #3868-3874. Aired: 06/08/88-06/16/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 436)
  - Prod. #3875-3881. Aired: 06/17/88-06/27/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 437)